Okay, so, let's talk about this problem of predicting the value of a house.
让我们继续讨论预测房价的问题
So, this is a very important problem, at least in the United States.
这是一个很重要的问题 至少对美国而言很重要
It's estimated that household wealth is nearly 50% invested in real estate.
据估计 美国家庭会把在房地产投资50%的财产
So, this is clearly important.
显然 房产价格就变成了一个很重要的问题
Both to consumers, individuals, as well as policy makers.
对于消费者 个人 或者说是政策制定者 都很重要
Okay, so I'm here and I wanna sell my house.
打个比方 我想卖房子了
I have this nice, big, lime green house, but I don't know how much to list it for.
我有一栋 又大又好 绿黄色的房子 但是我不知道还有什么值得说的
So I'm not sure what value my house has, and so
我也不知道我房子的价值
how do I think about estimating the value of the house?
也不知道该如何预估我房子的价值
Well, it might make sense that what I do is I look
如果我去看一些邻居最近出售房子的售价
at other recent sales that have occurred in my neighborhood.
来预估我房子的售价 是一件很合理的事
So I look locally, at the region around me, and
对于 一块离我很近的区域
I say how much are the other houses sold for and what do those houses look like?
我想知道那些房子卖了多少 和那些房子长什么样
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna record for
我要做的就是 把那些房子记录下来
each one of these recent sales what was the sales price?
每一间房子的售价是多少
And also, what was the size of the house that was sold?
还有那些房子的面积是多少
I'm gonna say that that's what signifies whether that house is similar to mine
我想说的是 最重要的事那些房子是否和我的房子差不多
or not.
还是不一样
Okay, so being a statistician, I'm gonna take all these observations I had and
作为一名统计学家 我将要把我观测到的这些值
I'm gonna make a plot of them.
把他们绘制出来
So in the US at least, the size of the house is measured by square feet.
在美国房屋的面积的单位是平方尺
So that's gonna be my x axis.
所以这就是我的X轴
And then my y axis is gonna be the sales price of the house.
y轴是我房屋的售价
Okay, so that's my y variable and
这就是我的变量y
each one of these points represents some individual house sale.
每一个点代表着一所房子的售价
So here this is one previous house sale in my neighborhood.
这个点是 我附近区域最近卖出的售价
And just to introduce a little bit of terminology here when we're
这边我们会用到一些术语 就是
talking about regression, people often refer to x, this variable x,
当我们说到回归的时候 人们会说到x 也就是变量x
as being the feature, that's the terminology we've been using.
作为特征 这也就是我们要使用的术语
People also talk about it being the covariate or the predictor,
人们也会叫做协变量或者说自变量
and in some cases, it's called the independent variable.
有时候也叫作独立变量
And then our observation y is as I've just said,
而我们的y 我刚才说的
I tend to refer to it as an observation.
我更倾向于叫做观测值
People also call it a response or the dependent variable.
有时候人们会叫做 因变量
Okay, so
好的 那么
the question is how am I gonna use these observations to estimate my house value?
那么问题就是 我如何使用这些观测值来预测我的房价呢
Well I might look at how big my house is and
我会看一下我房子大概有多少面积
look for other sales of houses of that size.
然后找到那个面积房子的售价
Well, most likely there are gonna be exactly zero house
大部分情况下 很少会有
sales of other houses that had exactly the same square footage as my house.
出售的房子和我的房子的面积一模一样的情况
Okay, so I say well I can't use this approach.
所以我不能用这种方法
I'm gonna be a little bit more flexible and
我会用更加灵活的方法
I'm gonna look at some neighborhood, not geographic neighborhood some little range
我会看我附近的住宅 不光光是地理位置上的附近
of square footage around my actual square footage here.
而是指 房屋面积和我差不多大小的房子
So I'm going to say okay let's look at all house sales that were for
所以我要说的是 让我们看一下房子
houses within this range of square footage.
在一定范围面积的售价
But even with that approach, in this case for example,
即使通过这种方法 在这个例子中
I only have two house sales that I'm gonna base my estimate off of.
我们会看到有两所房子处于这个区间 而我们用这两个点预测
So I don't really feel very comfortable with that.
我觉得有点不太好
And what I'm actually doing here is I'm throwing out all these other observations
我将要做的是把别的观测值都删掉
as if they had nothing to do with the value of my house.
因为他们和我要预测的房屋售价一点关系都没有
And the question is, is that reasonable?
问题是 这个合理吗?
Do we actually believe that there's actually no information
我们是否真的觉得
in these other observations?
别的观测值一点信息都不包括吗?
Well, when I look at this data and when I think about data I like to leverage all
当我们看数据的时候 并且思考数据的时候
the information that I can to come up with good predictions.
我需要把所有信息都考虑到才能得出良好的预测结果 翻译 tod | 审阅 PhoenixLIU Global Coursera Translator Community